Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
Cornell Migrant Program records, [ca. 1953-2005]
- Series XV. Government Bodies and Groups
  - Governor's Task Force on Agricultural Employment, Education and Labor - drafts and correspondence, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Farm Employment Project Report (Dairy), 1989 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Governor's task force report, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Governor's task force - Cornell Cooperative Extension response, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Agricultural Labor Markets in New York State and Implications For Labor Policy - Cornell, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - New York State Department of Labor - MSFW Coordinated Enforcement Program, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Coordination of migrant farmworkeres service programs - Martin, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Child labor, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Study of the farm labor contractor system in New York State, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Migrant Education Council of New York State, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - ICC on Farmworkers - Meeting in Wayne County, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - State and federal regulations - ICC, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Worker Protection Act amendments, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - United State Department of Labor- Region II Pre-Harvest conference, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - New York State Senate memorandum on farmworkers, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - New York State joint legislative hearing on farmworkers, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Testimony before the New York State joint legislature hearing, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Testimony before the New York State joint legislature hearing, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Separate and Unequal: New York's Farmworkers - New York State Senate, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Senator Mendez (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Drinking water legislation - New York State, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Increasing Understanding of Public Problems and Policies - Martin, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Child Labor in Agriculture - GAO, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Washington Line - AFOP newsletter, 1994 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Washington Newsline - AFOP newsletter, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Washington Newsline - AFOP newsletter, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Washington Newsline - AFOP newsletter, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Washington Line - Association of Farmworker Opportunity Programs (AFOP), 1998 (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Washington Newsline - Association of Farmworker Opportunity Programs (AFOP) newsletter, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 61)
- Series XVI. Immigration
  - Border patrol activities, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Formulation of Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA), 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) - Sanctions, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Impact of New Immigration Reform Bill - Miller, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) - Legalization Program (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - SAW application (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Western New York Immigration Action Coalition Committee minutes, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Western New York Immigration Action Coalition, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - New immigration law presentation - Embrey, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Work authorization (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Reporting Requirements- SAWS, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Employment discrimination, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) correspondence - Embrey, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Replenishment Agricultural Worker (RAW) Program, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Temporary status To permanent status, 1988, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Family fairness, 1989, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Immigration act, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) efforts by the United States Department of Agriculture, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Immigrants and public benefits, 1987-1991 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Rights of undocumented workers, 1991, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Undocumented children and the school, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Avoiding immigration discrimination in agriculture - Leaders guide, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project proposal - New York State, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project contract - New York State, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Anti-Discrimination workshops Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project monthly reports, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project correspondence - Embrey, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project: Northeast proposal not submitted, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Anti-Discrimination materials (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Anti-Discrimination presentation overheads (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project proposal (federal) with Farmworker Legal Services of New York (FLSNY), 1992 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project reports - Farmworker Legal Services of New York (FLSNY) submitted, 1992-1993 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project proposal, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Legal services subcontract and transfer, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Anti-Discrimination Project monthly reports, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Trainings for Cornell Cooperative Extension workshops - Pipkins, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension news articles on sanctions and discrimination - Embrey, 1992-1995 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Citizenship campaign report, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Becoming a Citizen - Training notebook - Embrey, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Citizenship trainings outline (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Citizenship project - news articles - Embery, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - 245 (i) Action Alert, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Assessment of Factors Affecting Employment of Temporary Foreign Workers in East Coast Apple Harvest - Holt, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Alien Workers in Agriculture: The Need for Policy Linkage - Martin, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - H-2A temporary program, 1987-1992 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - H-2A articles (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - "Albatrosss" of Immigration Reform: Temporary Worker Policy in United States - Briggs, School of Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 1987 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Briggs articles (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Illegal Immigration: Good for One and Good for All- Smith, School of Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR) (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - H-2A Program: Protections for United States Farmworkers, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Emerging Outcomes in California Agriculture and the Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) of 1986 - Rosenberg, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Unauthorized Immigration and Immigration Reform: Present Trends and Prospects - Portes, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Adverse Impact of Immigration on Florida's Farmworkers - Barry, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Embrey letter concerning the Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) impact in Wayne County, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Labor Expenditures Help Determine Farms Affected by Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRAC) - United States Department of Agriculture, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Efficiency and Equity as Goals for Contemporary United States Immigration Policy - Briggs, School of Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 1989 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Employer Sanction and the Question of Discrimination - Briggs, School of Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 1990 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - Immigration Timeline - Embrey, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Unskilled, Non-Immigrant Workers - Embrey, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Immigration Policy: Political or Economic - Briggs, School of Industrial and Labor Relations (ILR), 1991 (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Immigration Reform and Perishable Crop Agriculture Vol.1, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Immigration Reform and Perishable Crop Agriculture Vol.II, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA): The Effects of Employer Sanctions and Legalization on Wages - United States Department of Labor, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Circular Mobility, Migrant Communities and Policy Restrictions: Unauthorized Flows From Mexico - United States Department of Labor, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act (IRCA) papers by E. Figueroa, 1991. 1993 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Foreign farmworkers in United States - Government Accountability Office (GAO) action needed to protect Florida sugar cane workers, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Advocates Quick Reference Guide to Immigration Research - LaRaza, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Commission on Immigration Reform, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - H-2A Agricultural Guest Worker Program: Changes Could Improve Services to Employers and Better Protect Workers - Government Accountability Office (GAO), 1997 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - H-2A: Experiences of Individual Vidalia Onion Growers - Government Accountability Office (GAO), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 70)
  - Briggs interview - Embrey, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 71)
  - INS raids vigil at Batavia, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 72)
- Series XVII. WARE
  - WARE flyer (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Agenda/Process Committee, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Membership lists, 1980-1989 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - WARE committee lists, 1985-1987 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - WARE newsletters and meetings notices, 1985-1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Newsletters, 1992-2000 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Rethink Columbus Day articles, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Education subcommittee, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Summer curriculum course - Shay, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Financial aid workshop for parents, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Shay's course materials, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Boces In-service Day: WARE workshops, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Proposed institute for teachers, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - School recruitment and hiring committee, 1985-1988 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - News articles on WARE (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - WARE editorial concerning King beating (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Paton's super duper hiring, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Parent involvement committee, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Racism workshop for members, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Dr. Kunjufu at N. Rose Wolcott, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Dr. Kunjufu at Sodus (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Dr. Kunjufu at Williamson, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Kunjufu community meetings (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - N. Rose-Wolcott Kunjufu and counseling position, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - N. Rose-Wolcott parent group, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Dr. Kunjufu parent workshop, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Sodus school hiring and recruitment, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Multicultural educational resources - WARE folder 1, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Multicultural educational resources - folder 2 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Multicultural educational resources - folder 3 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - School job bank, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Apple Blossom Dinner, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Meetings of related groups (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Martin Luther King Day - PreWARE (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Martin Luther King commission, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Martin Luther King Day, 2001 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Tim Barber (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Tim Barber Scholarship (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Dr. Anderson's course, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Mrs. Winifred Hodge, Lyons oral interview, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Division of Civil Rights meeting notes, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - WARE proposed workshop for superintendent, 1989? (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Regents curriculum of inclusion and reactions, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - Criminal justice group, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - WARE/Sodus School mentoring project, 1988-1989 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - WARE mentoring project, 1989-1993 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Lyons Youth Needs - W/WARE (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Sodus "RIOT", 1990 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - First African American student dinner, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Pancake breakfast, 1990 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Recognition dinner, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - African American recognition dinner, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - NAACP Wayne County newsletter and reorganization, 1990, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 68)
  - Lyons Concerned Citizens (Box 18, Folder 69)
  - Dr. Cooper workshop, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 70)
  - School superintendents meeting, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 71)
  - Meetings with Dr. Walter Cooper, Board of Regents, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 72)
  - WARE educational accomplishments (Box 18, Folder 73)
  - Liberty Partnership proposal- not funded, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 74)
  - Youth speak out, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 75)
  - Joey Stewart (Box 18, Folder 76)
  - John Joyce (Box 18, Folder 77)
  - Anti-racism training, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 78)
  - Red Creek School board, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 79)
  - Sodus School Review, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 80)
  - Haitian farmworkers and Walmart - Beating, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 81)
  - Walmart demonstration, 1996-11-02 (Box 18, Folder 82)
  - Newark police task force, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 83)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension and WARE, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 84)
  - Race and WARE: news articles, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 85)
  - Jean Francois vs. Newark Police Trail, 1999 (Box 18, Folder 86)
- Series XVIII. Migrant Education Clippings and News/Views
  - Clippings, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - News/Views, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - News/Views, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - News/Views, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - News/Views, 1981 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - News/Views, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - News/Views, 1983-2, 1983-06 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - News/Views, 1983-08, 1983-10, 1983-12 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - News/Views, 1984-04, 1984-06 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - News/Views, 1984-08, 1984-10, 1984-12 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - News/Views, 1985-02, 1985-04, 1985-06 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - News/Views, 1985-08, 1985-10, 1985-12 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - News/Views, 1986-02, 1986-04-1986-06 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - News/Views, 1986-08, 1986-10, 1986-12 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - News/Views, 1987-02, 1987-04, 1987-06 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - News/Views, 1987-08, 1987-10, 1987-12 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - News/Views, 1988-02, 1988-04, 1988-06 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - News/Views, 1988-08, 1988-10, 1988-12 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - News/Views, 1989-2, 1989-04, 1989-06 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - News/Views, 1989-08, 1989-10, 1989-12 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - News/Views, 1990-02, 1990-04, 1990-06 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - News/Views, 1990-08, 1990-10, 1990-12 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - News/Views, 1991-02, 1991-04, 1991-06 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - News/Views, 1991-08, 1991-10 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Series XIX. News/Views 1992-2000
  - News/Views, 1992-02, 1992-04, 1992-06 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - News/Views, 1992-08, 1992-10, 1992-12 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - News/Views, 1993-02, 1993-04, 1993-06 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - News/Views, 1993-08, 1993-10, 1993-12 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - News/Views, 1994-02, 1994-04, 1994-07 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - News/Views, 1994-09, 1994-12 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - News/Views, 1995-03, 1995-07 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - News/Views, 1995-09, 1995-12 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - News/Views, 1996-03, 1996-07 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - News/Views, 1996-09, 1996-12 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - News/Views, 1997-04, 1997-08 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - News/Views, 1997-09, 1997-12 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - News/Views, 1998-04, 1998-07, 1998-09 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - News/Views, 1999-03, 1999-06 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - News/Views, 1999-09, 1999-12 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - News/Views, 2000-03, 2000-06 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - News/Views, 2000-09, 2000-12 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Series XX: Farm Labor Research (by person's name)
  - Don Barr (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Vernon Briggs papers, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Rose Marie Chierici, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lance Compa (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Compa - Worker's Freedom of Association, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Clete Daniel (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Maralyn Edid (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Herb Engman (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Bernard Erven, Ohio State (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Janet Fitchen (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Victor Garcia (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Luin Goldring (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Goldstein - Farmworkers Justice Fund (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - David Griffith - Papers on east coast workers (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Cindy Hahamovitch (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Monica Heppel (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Heppel dissertation (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Heppel dissertation (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Ed Kissam (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Farm Labor Supply Study - Kissam and Griffith, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Phil Martin (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Martin newsletters (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Changing Face of Rural America Conference - Iowa, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Changing Face Conference - Delaware, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Best Practices for Migrant Worker's Conference SOA Martin, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Changing Face of Rural California Conference Martin, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Rick Mines - Tradition of migration, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Demetrois Papademetriou (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Balancing Acts - Papademetriou and Heppel, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Max Pfeffer (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Refugio Rochin/Samora Center (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Rene Rosenbaum (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Gil Rosenberg, Kentucky (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Howard Rosenberg - Labor Management Decisions Newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Agricultural industrial relations bibliography (Box 21)
  - Demographic and employment profile of perishable crop farmworkers (Box 21)
  - Demographics, household composition, income and use of services (Box 21)
  - Migrant Farmworkers: Pursuing Security in an Unstable Labor Market (Box 21)
  - Low Skilled Immigrants in the Changing Labor Market, 1997 (Box 21)
- Series XXI. Cornell Extension Programs Related to Labor
  - Farm Labor Research, Dept of Rural Sociology (Box 22, Folder 1A)
  - Work Simplifications in Apple Packing Operations -Spencer/Blakeley (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Easing labor Problems Among New York State Grape Growers - Capener, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural careers - Tenney, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Enrique Figueroa (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Impact of Immigration Reform and Control Act on Farm Labor Contracting - Figueroa, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Ulster Community College pomology course - Gerling, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Dale Grossman (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Brian How, 1966-1982 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Jim Holt, New York discussion, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Jim Leonard, J and M Leonard Farm, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Presentations - Embrey see box 10, 1985-1988 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence with Farmworkers - Embrey (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Changes in New York State farm minimum, wage law - Maloney/Embrey, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Tom Maloney, CALS (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Human Resource Advisory Committee - Maloney, 1987-1996 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Multi-State Human Resource Management Group, 1989-1996 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Multi-State HRM Group Toronto meeting, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Human Resource Management Club, 1989-1990 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Eloy Rodriguez (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Chuck Russell, Russell Farms (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Extension Agents on Migrant Farmworkers (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Labor regulations meeting, 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Fruit farm business summary (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Labor management, 1980-1989 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extensino Human Resources Pilot Project - Embrey/Maloney (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Human Relations on the Farm - Bixby and LeClar (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Agent's Farm Labor - Related needs (survey) - Embrey /Babcock, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Human Relations on the Farm - Babcock, 1980-1989 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Involving Workers In Decisions - Babcock/Embrey, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Considerations Developing Farm Personal Management Program, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Western New York Fruit Advisory Committee, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Fruit/Vegetable Cornell Cooperative Extension Newsletter on Labor, 1983-2000s (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Farm management skills in-service, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Farm business management retreat, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Crop Management Association Sustainable Agriculture, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Mike Quality Incentives for Dairy Employees - Maloney, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Employee Training Practices on Large New York Dairy Farms - Maloney, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - Agricultural labor relations - Cornell Cooperative Extension meeting, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Agriculture employers rights, responsibilities, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Survey of Apple Farms in New York State, 1996 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Spaning milker training, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Grapes and labor (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Management of Hispanic employees on New York dairy farms survey, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Employee compensation and job satisfaction on dairy farms - Study, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Workforce development in production agriculture in-service, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - Managing Hispanic workers - Maloney, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - Education programs for agribusiness managers, 2003-2004 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Lead New York and NELD (Box 22, Folder 50)
  - CARDI (Box 22, Folder 51)
  - Agriculture in the classroom, 1998-2002 (Box 22, Folder 52)
  - Farm Net - Cornell Cooperative Extension (Box 22, Folder 53)
  - Farming alternatives (Box 22, Folder 54)
  - Sustainable agriculture and NYSAWG (Box 22, Folder 54)
- Series XXII. Immigration Policy and Reports
  - Shattuck Manifesto, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Guestworker legislation, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Amnesty proposal, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Ag jobs, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Dream Act, 2002-2003 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Drivers licenses (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Center for Migration Studies Conference, 1994 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Background - Center for Immigration Studies (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Immigration review - CIS (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - SCOPE - CIS (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - NAFTA/Free Trade and Farmworkers (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - National Immigration Law Center (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Center for Immigration Rights "Reports" Newsletter (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Immigration Rights Update newsletter (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - African Americans and immigration (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Research Perspective on Migration - Carnegie Newsletter (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Sierra Club on Immigration (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Shortage/No Shortage Farm Labor (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Wages and immigration (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Commission on Immigration Reform (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Immigration Reform and Control Act - James Holt (Box 23, Folder 21)